[
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "9401_BefriendHorse",
		"Type": "MountUnlock",
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "9401_Befriend_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "9401_Horse",
		"AchievementId": "MountType_Unlock_Horse",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "Expansion_2023_Unlock",
		"RequiredLevel": 1,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "9401_BefriendHorse_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9401_BefriendHorse_title",
		"Description": "@9401_BefriendHorse_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@9401_BefriendHorse_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9401_BefriendHorse_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_BefriendHorse_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_BefriendHorse_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "9401_TutorialFood",
		"Type": "MountUnlock",
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "9401_TutorialFood_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "9401_Horse",
		"AchievementId": "9401_TutorialComplete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "Expansion_2023_Unlock",
		"RequiredLevel": 1,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "9401_Tutorial_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@9401_TutorialFood_title",
		"Description": "@9401_TutorialFood_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@9401_TutorialFood_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9401_TutorialFood_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_TutorialFood_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_TutorialFood_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "9401_VectorWF",
		"Type": "MountUnlock",
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "9401_VectorWF_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "9402_Conman",
		"AchievementId": "9401_VectorWF_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "Expansion_2023_Unlock",
		"RequiredLevel": 1,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "9401_VectorWF_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9401_VectorWF_title",
		"Description": "@9401_VectorWF_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@9401_VectorWF_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9401_VectorWF_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_VectorWF_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_VectorWF_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "9403_VectorWolves",
		"Type": "MountUnlock",
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "9403_VectorWolves_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "9403_Wolf",
		"AchievementId": "9403_VectorWolves_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "Expansion_2023_Unlock",
		"RequiredLevel": 1,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "9403_VectorWolves_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9403_VectorWolves_title",
		"Description": "@9403_VectorWolves_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@9403_VectorWolves_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9403_VectorWolves_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9403_VectorWolves_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9403_VectorWolves_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "9403_FreeWolves",
		"Type": "MountUnlock",
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "9403_FreeWolves_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "9403_Wolf",
		"AchievementId": "MountType_Unlock_DireWolf",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "Expansion_2023_Unlock",
		"RequiredLevel": 1,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "9403_FreeWolves_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9403_FreeWolves_title",
		"Description": "@9403_FreeWolves_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@9403_FreeWolves_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9403_FreeWolves_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9403_FreeWolves_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9403_FreeWolves_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "9403_VectorBS",
		"Type": "MountUnlock",
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "9403_VectorBS_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "9404_Record",
		"AchievementId": "9403_VectorBS_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "Expansion_2023_Unlock",
		"RequiredLevel": 1,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "9403_VectorBS_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9403_VectorBS_title",
		"Description": "@9403_VectorBS_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@9403_VectorBS_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9403_VectorBS_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9403_VectorBS_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9403_VectorBS_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "9403_VectorLions",
		"Type": "MountUnlock",
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "9403_VectorLions_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "9405_Lion",
		"AchievementId": "9403_VectorLions_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9404_T4_15_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 1,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "9403_VectorLions_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9403_VectorLions_title",
		"Description": "@9403_VectorLions_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@9403_VectorLions_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9403_VectorLions_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9403_VectorLions_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9403_VectorLions_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "9405_RescueLion",
		"Type": "MountUnlock",
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "9405_RescueLion_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "9405_Lion",
		"AchievementId": "MountType_Unlock_Sabretooth",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9403_VectorLions_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 1,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "9405_RescueLion_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9401_RescueLion_title",
		"Description": "@9405_RescueLion_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@9405_RescueLion_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9405_RescueLion_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9405_RescueLion_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9405_RescueLion_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "EF_Tour_0",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "9401_FirstRace_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "9401_Horse",
		"AchievementId": "EF_Tour_0_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "MountType_Unlock_Horse",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "EF_Tour_0_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9401_Tour_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@9401_FirstRace_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9401_FirstRace_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_FirstRace_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_FirstRace_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "EF_Rally_1",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "EF_Rally_1_Container",
		"AchievementId": "EF_Rally_1_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "MountType_Unlock_Horse",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "EF_Rally_1_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9401_Rally_1_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Rally_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9401_Rally_1_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Rally_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Rally_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "EF_Rally_2",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "EF_Rally_2_Container",
		"AchievementId": "EF_Rally_2_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "MountType_Unlock_Horse",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "EF_Rally_2_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9401_Rally_2_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Rally_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9401_Rally_2_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Rally_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Rally_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "EF_Tour_1",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "EF_Tour_1_Container",
		"AchievementId": "EF_Tour_1_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "MountType_Unlock_Horse",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "EF_Tour_1_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9401_Tour_1_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9401_Tour_1_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Tour_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Tour_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "EF_Tour_2",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "EF_Tour_2_Container",
		"AchievementId": "EF_Tour_2_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "MountType_Unlock_Horse",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "EF_Tour_2_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9401_Tour_2_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9401_Tour_2_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Tour_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Tour_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "EF_Tour_3",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "EF_Tour_3_Container",
		"AchievementId": "EF_Tour_3_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "MountType_Unlock_Horse",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "EF_Tour_3_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9401_Tour_3_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9401_Tour_3_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Tour_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Tour_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "WF_Rally_1",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "WF_Rally_1_Container",
		"AchievementId": "WF_Rally_1_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9401_T1_5_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "WF_Rally_1_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9402_Rally_1_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Rally_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9402_Rally_1_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Rally_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Rally_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "WF_Rally_2",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "WF_Rally_2_Container",
		"AchievementId": "WF_Rally_2_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9401_T1_5_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "WF_Rally_2_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9402_Rally_2_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Rally_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9402_Rally_2_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Rally_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Rally_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "WF_Tour_1",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "WF_Tour_1_Container",
		"AchievementId": "WF_Tour_1_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9401_T1_5_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "WF_Tour_1_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9402_Tour_1_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9402_Tour_1_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Tour_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Tour_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "WF_Tour_2",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "WF_Tour_2_Container",
		"AchievementId": "WF_Tour_2_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9401_T1_5_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "WF_Tour_2_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9402_Tour_2_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9402_Tour_2_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Tour_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Tour_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "WF_Tour_3",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "WF_Tour_3_Container",
		"AchievementId": "WF_Tour_3_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9401_T1_5_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "WF_Tour_3_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9402_Tour_3_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9402_Tour_3_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Tour_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Tour_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "GC_Rally_1",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "GC_Rally_1_Container",
		"AchievementId": "GC_Rally_1_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9402_T2_10_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "GC_Rally_1_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9403_Rally_1_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Rally_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9403_Rally_1_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Rally_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Rally_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "GC_Rally_2",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "GC_Rally_2_Container",
		"AchievementId": "GC_Rally_2_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9402_T2_10_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "GC_Rally_2_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9403_Rally_2_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Rally_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9403_Rally_2_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Rally_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Rally_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "GC_Tour_1",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "GC_Tour_1_Container",
		"AchievementId": "GC_Tour_1_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9402_T2_10_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "GC_Tour_1_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9403_Tour_1_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9403_Tour_1_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Tour_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Tour_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "GC_Tour_2",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "GC_Tour_2_Container",
		"AchievementId": "GC_Tour_2_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9402_T2_10_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "GC_Tour_2_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9403_Tour_2_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9403_Tour_2_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Tour_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Tour_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "GC_Tour_3",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "GC_Tour_3_Container",
		"AchievementId": "GC_Tour_3_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9402_T2_10_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "GC_Tour_3_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9403_Tour_3_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9403_Tour_3_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Tour_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Tour_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "BS_Rally_1",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "BS_Rally_1_Container",
		"AchievementId": "BS_Rally_1_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9403_T3_15_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "BS_Rally_1_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9404_Rally_1_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Rally_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9404_Rally_1_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Rally_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Rally_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "BS_Rally_2",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "BS_Rally_2_Container",
		"AchievementId": "BS_Rally_2_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9403_T3_15_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "BS_Rally_2_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9404_Rally_2_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Rally_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9404_Rally_2_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Rally_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Rally_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "BS_Tour_1",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "BS_Tour_1_Container",
		"AchievementId": "BS_Tour_1_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9403_T3_15_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "BS_Tour_1_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9404_Tour_1_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9404_Tour_1_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Tour_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Tour_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "BS_Tour_2",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "BS_Tour_2_Container",
		"AchievementId": "BS_Tour_2_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9403_T3_15_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "BS_Tour_2_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9404_Tour_2_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9404_Tour_2_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Tour_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Tour_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "BS_Tour_3",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "BS_Tour_3_Container",
		"AchievementId": "BS_Tour_3_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9403_T3_15_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "BS_Tour_3_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9404_Tour_3_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9404_Tour_3_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Tour_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Tour_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "EW_Rally_1",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "EW_Rally_1_Container",
		"AchievementId": "EW_Rally_1_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9404_T4_15_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "EW_Rally_1_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9405_Rally_1_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Rally_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9405_Rally_1_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Rally_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Rally_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "EW_Rally_2",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "EW_Rally_2_Container",
		"AchievementId": "EW_Rally_2_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9404_T4_15_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "EW_Rally_2_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9405_Rally_2_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Rally_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9405_Rally_2_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Rally_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Rally_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "EW_Tour_1",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "EW_Tour_1_Container",
		"AchievementId": "EW_Tour_1_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9404_T4_15_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "EW_Tour_1_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9405_Tour_1_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9405_Tour_1_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Tour_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Tour_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "EW_Tour_2",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "EW_Tour_2_Container",
		"AchievementId": "EW_Tour_2_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9404_T4_15_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "EW_Tour_2_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9405_Tour_2_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9405_Tour_2_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Tour_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Tour_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "EW_Tour_3",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "EW_Tour_3_Container",
		"AchievementId": "EW_Tour_3_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9404_T4_15_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "EW_Tour_3_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9405_Tour_3_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@94_ReadRules_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9405_Tour_3_Proposal_2",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Tour_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Tour_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "9401_Races",
		"Type": "MountUnlock",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "9401_Races_Quest",
		"NpcDestinationId": "9401_Horse",
		"AchievementId": "9401_T1_5_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9401_TutorialComplete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "9401_T1_5_Races_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9401_Races_title",
		"Description": "@9401_EFCircuit_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@9401_EFCircuit_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9401_EFCircuit_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_EFCircuit_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_EFCircuit_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "9402_Races",
		"Type": "MountUnlock",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "9402_Races_Quest",
		"NpcDestinationId": "9402_Conman",
		"AchievementId": "9402_T2_10_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9401_VectorWF_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "9402_T2_10_Races_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9402_Races_title",
		"Description": "@9402_Races_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@9401_WFCircuit_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9401_WFCircuit_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_WFCircuit_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_WFCircuit_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "9403_Races",
		"Type": "MountUnlock",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "9403_Races_Quest",
		"NpcDestinationId": "9403_Wolf",
		"AchievementId": "9403_T3_15_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9403_FreeWolves_complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "9403_T3_15_Races_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9403_Races_title",
		"Description": "@9403_WolfRaces_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@9403_WolfRaces_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9403_WolfRaces_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9403_WolfRaces_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9403_ValenciaIznov_02_Dialogue",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "9404_Races",
		"Type": "MountUnlock",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "9404_Races_Quest",
		"NpcDestinationId": "9404_Record",
		"AchievementId": "9404_T4_15_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9403_VectorBS_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "9404_T4_15_Races_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9404_Races_title",
		"Description": "@9403_BSRaces_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@9403_BSRaces_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9403_BSRaces_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9403_BSRaces_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9403_BSRaces_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "9405_Races",
		"Type": "MountUnlock",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "9405_Races_Quest",
		"NpcDestinationId": "9405_Lion",
		"AchievementId": "9405_T5_15_Races_Complete",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "9405_RescueLion_Complete",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "9405_T5_15_Races_Success",
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9405_Races_title",
		"Description": "@9405_LionRaces_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@9405_LionRaces_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9405_LionRaces_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9405_LionRaces_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9405_LionRaces_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "MountRace_ScaleTest_1",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "MountRace_ScaleTest_1_Container",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9404_Tour_6_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@9403_Tour_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9401_Tour_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Tour_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Tour_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "MountRace_ScaleTest_2",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "MountRace_ScaleTest_2_Container",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9404_Tour_6_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@9403_Tour_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9401_Tour_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Tour_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Tour_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "MountRace_ScaleTest_1_Short",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "MountRace_ScaleTest_1_Short_Container",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9404_Tour_6_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@9403_Tour_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9401_Tour_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Tour_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Tour_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "MountRace_ScaleTest_2_Short",
		"Type": "MountRace",
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "MountRace_ScaleTest_2_Short_Container",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@9404_Tour_6_title",
		"Description": "@9401_Tour_description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@9403_Tour_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9401_Tour_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@9401_Tour_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9401_Tour_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	}
]